<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Geekulcha Activities</string>
    <string name="action_settings">About</string>
    <string name="lorem2"> Hackathon is an annual event that takes places for Africa developer ecosystem.
        It’s a 42 hours challenge that gathers different
        students under one roof so they can solves challenges using technology.
 </string>
    <string name="lorem"> AI Masterclass is a program of five workshops and three live
        sessions about Artificial
        Intelligence brought to you by some of the best AI experts at Facebook.
    </string>
    <string name="lorem3"> An event that takes places for Africa developer ecosystem.
        It’s a 42 hours challenge that gathers different
        students under one roof so they can solves challenges using technology.
        Facilitated by Geekulcha on behalf of the GIZ in Johannesburg.
 </string>

    <string name="lorem4">
        Cloud OnBoard is a free, full-day training event, conveniently hosted in a city near you. Our instructors lead in-depth technical presentations and demonstrations to help you learn industry best practices and tips.
        Google Cloud Platform training accelerates your understanding of and ability to use the Google Cloud Platform services.
    </string>


    "\n"<string name="lorem5">
      The Science Forum South Africa 2017 will take place during 7 – 8 December at the CSIR International Convention Centre, Pretoria, South Africa.
The Science Forum South Africa is inspired by events such as ESOF, AAAS, and the Japan Agora. "\n"


The key objectives of the Forum remain:"\n"

"\n"To create a platform for a vibrant debate on the role of science, technology and innovation in society;"\n"
"\n"To promote international science, technology and innovation partnerships; and "\n"
To create a platform for key science, technology and innovation actors, including senior government leaders, academics, scientists, industry, civil society, and students to interact.
    </string>


    <string name="lorem6">
        Data Science for Impact and Decision Enablement (DSIDE)
DSIDE recruits vacation students over the period of June/July (Phase 1 - lasting 4 weeks)
        and continuing December/January (Phase 2 - lasting 8 weeks)."\n"

"\n" The programme is hosted at the CSIR. The aim of the programme is to support capacity building in the ever growing field of data science by scheduling recruits to participate
        in mentor-guided and learn-by-doing problem solving of real-world needs as presented by different stakeholders.
    </string>


</resources>
